Finding Aid for University of Michigan Board of Regents Portrait Collection, ca. 1860-ca. 1970
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
University of Michigan Board of Regents Portrait Collection circa 1860-1970
University of Michigan Board of Regents portrait collection
93297 Bimu 2
Portraits of some members of the University of Michigan Board of Regents.
0.4 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Brought together from various sources.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open for research.
The regents portrait collection was assembled from a variety of sources by Bentley Historical Library staff.
This collection contains portraits of about 65 members of the University of Michigan Board of Regents. Most of the portraits are of regents who served between about 1870 and 1970, although a few earlier regents are also included.
Other portraits of regents are found in the papers of individual regents.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Baits, Vera Burridge, 1892-1963.; Barbour, Levi L. (Levi Lewis), 1840-1925.; Beal, Junius E. (Junius Emery), 1860-1942.; Bentley, Alvin M. (Alvin Morell), 1918-1969.; Bishop, Russell Spencer, 1886-1946.; Blair, Austin, 1818-1894.; Briggs, Robert Peter, 1903-; Brown, Robert J., 1904-1985.; Burt, Hiram Austin, b. 1839.; Butterfield, Roger Williams, b. 1844.; Carey, Harry Westronae, 1850-1911.; Clements, William L. (William Lawrence), 1861-1934.; Cocker, W. J. (William Johnson), 1846-1901.; Codd, George Pierre, 1869-1927.; Comstock, William Alfred, 1877-1949.; Connable, Alfred B. (Alfred Barnes), 1904-; Cook, Franklin Mead, 1863-; Cook, Peter Napoleon, b. 1840.; Cram, Esther Marsh.; Crowley, David Henry, 1882-; Cudlip, William B., 1904-1988; Cutcheon, Byron M., 1836-1908.; Dean, Henry Stewart, 1830-1915.; Doan, Leland Ira, 1894-1974.; Eckert, Otto E., 1890-; Estabrook, Joseph, 1820-1894.; Fletcher, Frank Ward, 1853-1922.; Grant, Claudius Buchanan, 1835-1921.; Green, Sanford M. (Sanford Moon), 1807-1901.; Grosvenor, Ebenezer Oliver, 1820-1910.; Hanchett, Benjamin Sawtell, 1868-1933.; Hayward, Ralph A., 1895-1951.; Hebard, Charles, 1831-1902.; Hemans, Charles Fitch, 1896-; Herbert, J. Joseph, 1894-1956.; Hill, Arthur, 1847-1909.; Howard, Henry, 1833-1894.; Joy, James F. (James Frederick), 1810-1896.; Kearsley, Jonathan, 1786-1859.; Kiefer, Hermann, 1825-1911.; Kipke, Harry G., 1899-1972.; Knappen, Loyal Edwin, 1854-1930.; Leland, Frank Bruce.; Lynch, John David, 1890-1946.; McClelland, Robert, 1807-1880.; McInally, William Keith, 1905-1964.; McIntyre, Donald, 1807-1891.; Mason, Stevens Thomson, 1811-1843.; Matthaei, Frederick Carl, 1925-; Murfin, James Orin, 1875-1940.; Murphy, Irene Ellis, 1900-; Norris, Lyman, 1823-1894.; Palmer, Charles Henry, 1814-1887.; Pitcher, Zina, 1797-1872.; Sawyer, Walter H. (Walter Hulme), 1861-1931.; Shearer, James, 1823-1896.; Sill, John Mahelm Berry, 1831-1901.; Smith, Richard Root, 1869-1940.; Spaulding, Mr. (Oliver Lyman), 1833-1922.; Stevens, Kenneth Molyneaux, 1892-; Stockwell, Cyrus M. (Cyrus Moses), 1823-1899.; Stone, Ralph, 1868-1956.; University of Michigan. Board of Regents--Portraits.; Walker, Edward Carey, 1820-1894.; White, Peter, 1830-1908.; Whitman, Charles Rudolphus, b. 1847.; Willett, Charles Joseph, b. 1849.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Portraits
  - Baits, Vera Burridge, 1892-1963 (Box 1)
  - Barbour Levi L. (Levi Lewis), 1840-1925 (Box 1)
  - Beal, Junius Emery, 1860-1942 (Box 1)
  - Bentley, Alvin M. (Alvin Morell), 1918-1969 (Box 1)
  - Bishop, Russell Spencer, 1886- (Box 1)
  - Blair, Austin, 1818-1894 (Box 1)
  - Briggs, Robert Peter, 1903- (Box 1)
  - Brown, Robert J., 1904-1985 (Box 1)
  - Burt, Hiram Austin, b. 1839 (Box 1)
  - Butterfield, Roger Williams, b. 1844 (Box 1)
  - Carey, Harry Westronae, 1850-1911 (Box 1)
  - Clements, William Lawrence, 1861-1934 (Box 1)
  - Cocker, William Johnson, 1846-1901 (Box 1)
  - Codd, George Pierre, 1869-1927 (Box 1)
  - Comstock, William Alfred, 1877-1949 (Box 1)
  - Connable, Alfred B. (Alfred Barnes), 1904- (Box 1)
  - Cook, Franklin Mead, 1863- (Box 1)
  - Cook, Peter Napoleon, b. 1840 (Box 1)
  - Cram, Esther Marsh (Box 1)
  - Crowley, David Henry, 1882- (Box 1)
  - Cudlip, William Byrnes, 1904- (Box 1)
  - Cutcheon, Byron Mac, 1836-1908 (Box 1)
  - Dean, Henry Stewart, 1830-1915 (Box 1)
  - Doan, Leland Ira, 1894-1974 (Box 1)
  - Eckert, Otto E., 1890- (Box 1)
  - Estabrook, Joseph, 1820-1894 (Box 1)
  - Fletcher, Frank Ward, 1853-1922 (Box 1)
  - Grant, Claudius Buchanan, 1835-1921 (Box 1)
  - Green, Sanford M. (Sanford Moon), 1807-1901 (Box 1)
  - Grosvenor, Ebenezer Oliver, 1820-1910 (Box 1)
  - Hanchett, Benjamin Sawtell, 1868-1933 (Box 1)
  - Hayward, Ralph A., 1895-1951 (Box 1)
  - Hebard, Charles., 1831-1902 (Box 1)
  - Hemans, Charles Fitch, 1896- (Box 1)
  - Herbert, J. Joseph, 1894-1956 (Box 1)
  - Hill, Arthur, 1847-1909 (Box 1)
  - Howard, Henry, 1833-1894 (Box 1)
  - Joy, James Frederick, 1810-1896 (Box 1)
  - Kearsley, Jonathan, 1786-1859 (Box 1)
  - Kiefer, Hermann, 1825-1911 (Box 1)
  - Kipke, Harry G., 1899-1972 (Box 1)
  - Knappen, Loyal Edwin, 1854-1930 (Box 1)
  - Leland, Frank Bruce (Box 1)
  - Lynch, John David, 1890-1946 (Box 1)
  - McClelland, Robert, 1807-1880 (Box 1)
  - McInally, William Keith, 1905-1964 (Box 1)
  - McIntyre, Donald, 1807-1891 (Box 1)
  - Mason, Stevens Thomson, 1811-1843 (Box 1)
  - Matthaei, Frederick Carl, 1925- (Box 1)
  - Murfin, James Orin, 1875-1940 (Box 1)
    (also in UAm)
  - Murphy, Irene Ellis, 1900- (Box 1)
  - Norris, Lyman, 1823-1894 (Box 1)
  - Palmer, Charles Henry, 1814-1887 (Box 1)
  - Pitcher, Zina, 1797-1872 (Box 1)
  - Sawyer, Walter H. (Walter Hulme), 1861-1931 (Box 1)
  - Shearer, James, 1823-1896 (Box 1)
  - Sill, John Mahelm Barry, 1831-1901 (Box 1)
  - Smith, Richard Root, 1869-1940 (Box 1)
  - Spaulding, Oliver Lyman, 1833-1922 (Box 1)
  - Stevens, Kenneth Molyneaux, 1892- (Box 1)
  - Stockwell, Cyrus Moses, 1823-1899 (Box 1)
  - Stone, Ralph, 1868-1956 (Box 1)
  - Walker, Edward Carey, 1820-1894 (Box 1)
  - White, Peter Quintard, 1830-1908 (Box 1)
  - Whitman, Charles Rudolphus, b. 1847 (Box 1)
  - Willett, Charles Joseph, b. 1849 (Box 1)